<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EOSurf</title>
    <link>http://eosurf.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EOSurf</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://eosurf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More than just surfing</title>
      <link>http://eosurf.com/post/more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eosurf.com/post/more/</guid>
      <description>At EOSurf you can look forward to sunsets on the beach, jungle hikes or hacking til dawn while connecting with people from all over the planet.
Discover your true potential while learning new skills and refining your talents. Here you can develop your dApp or bring your team for some EOS team building or networking. The idea is to leave inspired and energized to keep charging towards your goals.
Trips can be designed for both technical and non-technical audiences looking to understand EOS and blockchain technology and how it can be applied in a business setting or for expert EOS developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we offer</title>
      <link>http://eosurf.com/post/offer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eosurf.com/post/offer/</guid>
      <description>When you come to a EOSurf trip we plan everything from the moment you step off the plane so that you can focus on your specific goals.
 Airport Transfers and Transportation
 Accommodations: hotels or house rental
 Awesome activities: Surf a wave, chill on the beach, hike in the jungle or simply get lost in telegram on a hammock. No matter what adventure you choose, we want the experiences to blend fun and work to transform the way you travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Trip Goals</title>
      <link>http://eosurf.com/post/included/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eosurf.com/post/included/</guid>
      <description>Trips can be customized to match specific goals. Some examples include:
 Development sprints
 Content creation through media coverage / film + photography
 Meetups and networking
 Costa Rica Crypto Interview
 Learning Sessions / Team Training
 Recharge and focus on general wellness (exercise, healthy food, relaxation)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is EOSurf ?</title>
      <link>http://eosurf.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eosurf.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>A whole new way to discover EOS and find the optimal balance between WORK and LIFE. Whether you’re a dApp developer, a block producer team, an adventurous token holder, or an executive looking to learn about EOS, you are welcome to join us. EOSurf allows you to participate in the EOS ecosystem while staying in a beautiful country, working, staying active and networking with other EOS professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://eosurf.com/itineraries/itineraries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eosurf.com/itineraries/itineraries/</guid>
      <description>s&amp;mdash; title: &amp;ldquo;Sample Itineraries&amp;rdquo; date: 2017-09-01T17:39:43+02:00
draft: false When you come to a EOSurf trip we take care of everything from the moment you step off the plane so that you can focus on your team specific goals. Here’s exactly what’s included in your stay…
 Airport Transfers: We’ll transfer you to/from either Liberia or San Jose airport, or we can collect you from anywhere in Costa Rica, and bring you to the location, on whatever day works for you Accommodations: We recommend 4-5 nights in a shared or private hotels or house rental.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>